

PAUL DUFOUR

Software Engineer Internship

- @ paul.paul.dufour@gmail.com
- in dufour-paul kolowy
- Paris Lille, France
- ★ kolowy
- https://kolowy.fr/

LANGUAGES



Markdown

TOOLS



INFRASTRUCTURE AS CODE



LANGUAGES

French: Native language

English: TOEIC: 895

German: Notions - Exchange with German correspondents

from Saarlouis

INTERESTS

Sport: **Running Tennis** Windsurfing Hiking

Other qualifications: PSC1 (first aid training certifi-

OTHER EXPERIENCES

Hackaton #1:

Creation of an E-Accessibility Project - 2022

Sailing Instructor Assistant: Accompaniment of students on sailing techniques and freshwater navigation

Unity First Game Jam: Participation in the Unity Game Jam: improving a video game (1st place)

ABOUT ME

I am a 3rd year student in computer engineering. I am highly motivated to improve my learning. I have been passionate about computer science since I was 13 years old, and I am always looking for new things to discover! I would like to learn and develop my skills in infrastructure but remain open to all opportunitiesd

EDUCATION

Software Engineer EPITA Ecole Pour l'Informatique et les Techniques Avancées	2021 – now	Paris, France
ICE Chulalongkorn University Information and Communication Engineering, 5 months	≐ 2023	Bangkok, Thailand
French Baccalaureate Marcq Institution	ä 2021	Lille, France

EXPERIENCES

Teaching Assistant C Dièse Caml

2023 - now

EPITA

Teach C# and Caml to first-year students and create subjects and exercices for them.

Vittascience Internship | 🏶



Summer 2023

Paris, France

Create a Python to Block converter with Javascript.

Prologin Organization | 💖 | 🏶



2022 - now

Prologin

Secretary

Management of the association and registration of members.

Memher

- Girls Can Code! workshop to promote the integration of women in Computer Science
- Create a new website for Girls Can Code!
- Met with high-ranking officials to promote and develop the association and its actions
- Organization of a computer science contest where students under 21 have to solve problems and challenges.
- · Maintaining the association's infrastructure, develop new tools and maintain existing ones
- · Help in implementing a modern, code-compliant infrastructure with containerization of internal and external services.

PROJECTS

JWS - Java Web Service

february 2024

Introduction to development framworks (Quarkus and Hibernates) and software architectures in Java.

42SH | 🏶

ianuary 2024

EPITA

EPITA project to create a POSIX shell in C.

OCR Sudoku Solver | 😯 | 🏶









A project to create an Optical Character Recognition to solve Sudoku in C.